{
    "subject": "Marie_de'_Medici",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Henry_IV_of_France",
    "human_readable": "Marie de' Medici is married to Henry IV of France.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9886132478713989,
            "question": "Was Henry IV of France married to Marie de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9456647634506226,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Marie de' Medici and Henry IV of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8618656396865845,
            "question": "Who was Marie de' Medici married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8398218750953674,
            "question": "What was the name of the French king who was married to Marie de' Medici?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8271680474281311,
            "question": "Which queen was married to Henry IV of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7896495461463928,
            "question": "Who was the ruler that Marie de' Medici was married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7598944902420044,
            "question": "To whom did Marie de' Medici wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6956689953804016,
            "question": "What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5582283735275269,
            "question": "Who is known as Henry IV of France?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4641261696815491,
            "question": "Was Marie de' Medici a queen?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marie de' Medici is married to Henry IV of France.",
            "html": "yago_28171_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is known as Henry IV of France?",
            "html": "yago_28171_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Henry IV of France's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28171_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom did Marie de' Medici wed?",
            "html": "yago_28171_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28171_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents provide information about Marie de' Medici, including her marriage to King Henry IV of France in 1600. This supports the triple statement that Marie de' Medici is married to Henry IV of France."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Marie de' Medici being the Queen of France as the second wife of King Henry IV, which confirms that she was indeed married to Henry IV of France."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}